<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Siddharth Girdhar</title>
    <link>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://siddharthgir.github.io/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 x 1</title>
      <link>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/box_reid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/box_reid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1x1 is a package re-identification system that allows users to load images of unique packages with a tag into the system and then query with a new image of one of the inserted packages to identify which tag it was linked to. The system generates a fingerprint for each package by first isolating the package via background removal and then generating features through a color histogram, dimensions of the package and a contrastive encoder. These fingerprints can then be used to match images to package, as 2 images of the same package will have a similar fingerprint. In our tests, we are able to acheive above 90% accuracy in re-identifiying boxes for a test sample of 200+ boxes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/covid_rl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/covid_rl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Optimial Vaccine Distribution amongst countries suffering Covid-19 can be a challenging as countries with more cases need more vaccines while those with less cases need less vaccines. We implemented models to model the growth of Covid-19 in country using the SIRD model which is based on continous markov decision processes. Then we implemented a reinforcmenent learning agent that can choose the optimial vaccine distribution policy between countries per day depending on some fixed supply of vaccines to minimize total number of deaths between a chosen set of countries. Our agent is able to learn better policies than naive methods such as distributing vaccines based on the ratio of cases or a countries population, as it is able to understand how the cases in a country will change overtime. We implemented a webapp based on Heryoku and Figma to allow users to select their own scenarios of which countries to consider and train an agent to learn a policy for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project was implemented in 24 hours and won best use of google cloud for CuHacking.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAC</title>
      <link>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/whac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/whac/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Copying Robot</title>
      <link>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/human-following-robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://siddharthgir.github.io/project/human-following-robot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
